A Guide to the Christian de Duve papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 2009:084 FA934
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Université de Nancy, Nancy, France, 1975 October 6 (Box 7)
- Colloque, Pontamousson (France), 1975 October 6-10 (Box 7)
- World Health Organization (WHO) Meeting, Geneva, 1975 October 6-7 (Box 7)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 November (Box 7)
- International Symposium on "Phogosis and anti-inflammatory therapy", Milan, Farmitalia, 1975 November 29 (Box 7)
- Université de Liège, Docteur Honoris Causa, Liège, 1975 November 27 (Box 7)
- Panel Discussion, American Heart Association, Anaheim, California, 1975 November 17 (Box 7)
- ASCB (American Society for Cell Biology), San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1975 November 12 (Box 7)
- Lecture, Houston, Texas, 1975 November 10 (Box 7)
- Yale University, New Haven, Connecticut, 1975 November 6 (Box 7)
- Extinct Commitments, 1975 December-1976 February (Box 7)
- Lunch, Ambassade de France, Brussels, 1976 February 27 (Box 7)
- Colloquium, L'Administration de l'Enseignement Supérior et de la Recherche Scientifique, Brussels, 1976 February 26 (Box 7)
- Conference, "La Revolution Biologique", Les Amis de l' Universite de Louvain, Hotel de Ville de Nivelles, 1976 February 24 (Box 7)
- Conference, Gand, Belgique, 1976 February 23 (Box 7)
- Lunch, Rotary Club of Louvain, Louvain, Belgium, 1976 February 14 (Box 7)
- The Rockefeller University, 75th Anniversary Seminar for Science Writers, 1976 January 27 (Box 7)
- Conference, Faculte de Médecine, Gand, 1975 December 17 (Box 7)
- Cercle des Alumni de la Fondation Universitaire, 1975 December 15 (Box 7)
- Nobel Festivities, Stockholm, Sweden, 1975 December 7-11 (Box 7)
- Rotary Club Luncheon, Antwerp, Belgium, 1975 December 4 (Box 7)
- Extinct Commitments, 1976 March-May (Box 7)
- FG.17, Farmacologia de los Lisosomas (Audiotape) (Box 7)
- University of Washington, Seattle, Washington, 1976 May 28 (Box 7)
- Parasitology Meeting, 1976 May 26 (Box 7)
- Counsel Scientifique, Institut de Biologie Moleculaire, 1976 May 12 (Box 7)
- L'Inauguration du Palais des Académies Restauré-Académies Royales de Belgique, Bruxelles, 1976 May 12 (Box 7)
- Societe Medicale Belge de Saint-Luc Cercle de Bruxelles, Brussels, 1976 April 26 (Box 7)
- Académie Royale de Médecine, Brussels, 1976 April 24 (Box 7)
- Biochemische Analytik 76, Munich, Germany, 1976 April 9-13 (Box 7)
- Visit of Michel Woitrin to Rockefeller University (RU) (M.M.), 1976 April 8 (Box 7)
- Symposium on Drug Metabolism, University of Surrey, Guildford, England, 1976 April 6-8 (Box 7)
- Symposium, Fondation Médicale Reine Elizabeth, Brussels, 1976 April 7-10 (Box 7)
- Visit of the King and Queen of the Belgians to Yale University, New Haven, Connecticut, 1976 March 21-26 (Box 7)
- Lecture, Sloan-Kettering, New York, 1976 March 25 (Box 7)
- 75th Anniversary, The Rockefeller University, 1976 March 8 (Box 7)
- Extinct Commitments, 1976 June (Box 8)
- Pittsburgh, 1976 June 1 (Box 8)
- Arnold Lazarow Memorial Lecture, University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, 1976 June 2 (Box 8)
- Rockefeller University Convocation, 1976 June 6-8 (Box 8)
- German Society for Pathology, Freiburg, Germany, 1976 June 9 (Box 8)
- Meeting of the Advisory Board to the Max-Planck Institute for Immunobiology, Freiburg, 1976 June 11 (Box 8)
- WHO (World Health Organization) Meeting, ACMR (Advisory Committee on Medical Research), Geneva, 1976 June 21-25 (Box 8)
- Conferénce, Réunion Commune des Sociétes de Biochimie Belge et Française, Villeneuve d'Ascq., France, 1976 June 26 (Box 8)
- Extinct Commitments, 1976 September (Box 8)
- Congress on the Future of Medicine and "Mankind in the Third Millennium", Tygerberg, South Africa, 1976 September 26-30 (Box 8)
- Dinner with Raymond Velge, The Carlyle Hotel, New York City, 1976 September 20 (Box 8)
- First International Congress on Cell Biology, Boston, 1976 September 5-10 (Box 8)
- Fifth International Congress of Histochemistry and Cytochemistry, Bucharest, Romania, 1976 September 3 (Box 8)
- Colloque, "Biologie et Ethique", Brussels, 1976 September 2-4 (Box 8)
- Extinct Commitments, 1976 October-November (Box 8)
- Thesis Committee for Richard Sorace, Downstate Medical Center, Brooklyn, New York, 1976 October-November (Box 8)
- Lecture, Roche Institute of Molecular Biology, Nutley, New Jersry, 1976 November 18 (Box 8)
- Seminar, "Functions of Peroxisomes", Southwestern Medical School, 1976 November 16 (Box 8)
- Dallas/Fort Worth Regional Meeting, Dallas, Texas, 1976 November 16 (Box 8)
- Seminar, Albert Einstein College of Medicine, "Lysosomotropic Drugs, Bronx, New York, 1976 November 9 (Box 8)
- Connaissance et Vic d'Aujourd' hui, 1976 October 25 (Box 8)
- Pontifica Academia Scientiarum, Rome, 1976 October 18-23 (Box 8)
- Visit of Morris Ziff to the ICP, Brussels, 1976 October 19 (Box 8)
- American Association for the Study of the Liver, Annual Meeting (Albert Einstein, Chicago), 1976 November 5-6 (Box 8)
- Second South African Biochemistry Congress, Rustenburg, South Africa, 1976 October 4-8 (Box 8)
- Extinct Commitments, 1976 December-1977 March (Box 8)
- Earth Day, 1977 March 20 (Box 8)
- Conferénce, Sociéte Chimique de Belgique, Liège, Belgium, 1977 February 4 (Box 8)
- "L'Origine et l'Evolution de la Vie", Facultés Universitaires N.D. de la Paix, Namur, Belgique, 1977 March 1-2 (Box 8)
- USAID/WHO (World Health Organization) Workshops, Malaria Parasite, Rockefeller University, 1977 March 7-12 (Box 8)
- Conferénce, Société Général de Belgique, Bruxelles, 1977 March 3 (Box 8)
- Introduction to the Course of Cell Biology, Rockefeller University (RU), 1977 January 27 (Box 8)
- Christmas Lecture (Box 8)
- Alfred E. Mirsky Christmas Lectures, 1976 December 27-28 (Box 8)
- Institute of Biophysics, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1976 December 11-14 (Box 8)
- Universidad Nacional de Rosario-D. Honoris Causa, Rosario, Argentina, 1976 December 9-10 (Box 8)
- VI Latin American Congress of Pharmacology (6° Congreso Latinoamericano de Farmacología), Buenos Aires, 1976 December 6-8 (Box 8)
- Extinct Commitments, 1977 April-July (Box 9)
- XXVIII° Congrès International des Sciences Physiologiques, Paris, 1977 July 18-23 (Box 9)
- WHO (World Health Organization) Meeting, Geneva, 1977 June 13-17 (Box 9)
- Scientific Symposium, Fundamental Research and Human Cancer, Rockefeller University (RU), 1977 May 26 (Box 9)
- Cell Biology Course, Lysosomes or Peroxisomes. Rockefeller University (RU), 1977 June (Box 9)
- Symposium, Proteolysis, Demineralization and Other Degradative Processes in Human Biology and Disease, Farmington, Connecticut, 1977 May 19-20 (Box 9)
- Visit to Sandoz, Incorporated, East Hanover, New Jersey, 1977 May 11 (Box 9)
- Annual Postgraduate Lecture, Royal Postgraduate Medical School at Hammersmith Hospital, London, 1977 April 28 (Box 9)
- Visit to Weizmann Institute of Science, Rehovot, Israel, 1977 April 6-19 (Box 9)
- Extinct Commitments, 1977 September-December (Box 9)
- Symposium on Landmarks in Basic Biomedical Research, 1977 November 3-4 (Box 9)
- "The Role of Non-specific Immunity in the Prevention and Treatment of Cancer", Pontifical Academy of Sciences, Rome, Italy, 1977 October 17-21 (Box 9)
- Infectious Diseases Society of America, Americana Hotel, New York, 1977 October 10-11 (Box 9)
- "Liposomes and Their Uses in Biology and Medicine", NY Academy of Sciences, 1977 September 14-16 (Box 9)
- Extinct Commitments, 1977 September-December (Box 9)
- International Symposium on Tocopherol, Oxygen, and Biomembranes, Tokyo, Japan, 1977 September 1-4 (Box 9)
- Extinct Commitments, 1978 January-March (Box 9)
- Hotel Pierre, New York City, Technion's 25th Anniversary, 1978 September 27 (Box 9)
- Cori Lecture, Roswell Memorial Institute, Buffalo, 1978 September 19-20 (Box 9)
- "Evening at Rockefeller", 1978 May 31 (Box 9)
- Cours d' introduction á la biologie cellulaire, Institut de Recherches Cliniques de Montréal, 1978 May 25 (Box 9)
- 2nd Congress of the Pan American Association of Biochemical Societies, Caracas, Venezuela, 1978 September 3-9 (Box 9)
- Annual Distinguished Lecture in Pharmacology, "Lysosomotropic Therapy", Tulane University, School of Medicine, 1978 March 20 (Box 9)
- Gershon, David, Rockefeller University (RU), Tower 301, 1978 January 26 (Box 9)
- O'Hara Biochemical Research Symposia, "I. The Role of Compartmentation in Metabolic Regulation, Microenvironmental Aspects", Dallas, Texas, 1978 January 17 (Box 9)
- International Conference in Medicine, Bombay, India, 1978 January 8-11 (Box 9)
- Extinct Commitments, 1978 March-1979 December (Box 9)
- XIth International Congress of Biochemistry, Toronto, Canada, 1979 July 8-14 (Box 9)
- Cell Biology Course, Sloan Kettering, 1979 January 24 (Box 9)
- Rhône-Poulenc, 1979 December 4-7 (Box 9)
- Symposium at Monte Carlo, 1979 November 19-22 (Box 9)
- Lecture, New York University (NYU), 1979 November (Box 9)
- Conference at the Gerontological Center, Eisdorfer, 1978 September 29-30 (Box 9)
- Visit to Institute in Ljubljana, Yugoslavia, 1978 October 28-November 5 (Box 9)
- Syntex, 1978 October 18 (Box 9)
- Rockefeller University (RU), 1977 December 7 (Box 9)
- Belgium Today, Colloquium on [the] History of Centrifugal Fractionation, 1980 April 24 (Box 10)
- Extinct Commitments, 1980 (Box 10)
- Rutgers University, Nelson Distinguished Lectures in Biology, 1980 December 11 (Box 10)
- Medical Center Central Georgia, Speech, Macon, Georgia, 1980 September 29 (Box 10)
- VI Lofland Conference on Arterial Wall Metabolism, Bowman Gray School of Medicine of Wake Forest University, 1981 May 11 (Box 10)
- Conference on Lysosomes, Proctor Academy, Vermont, Gordon Conference, 1980 July 4 (Box 10)
- Mayo Clinic, Nick La Russo, 1980 May (Box 10)
- Association Belgo-Americaine, 1980 April (Box 10)
- Albert Einstein University, Department of Biochemistry, Seminar (Graduate Students), 1980 May 20 (Box 10)
- Symposium Atherogenesis, Vienna, 1980 April 7-12 (Box 10)
- University of California, Dedication of Gladstone Foundation Labs for Cardiovascular Research, 1980 March 31 (Box 10)
- Receptor Mediated Binding and Internalization of Toxins and Hormones, Medical Research Institute of Infectious Diseases, Fort Detrick, Maryland, 1980 March 24-25 (Box 10)
- Rockefeller University (RU), Tissue Fractionation Course, 1980 February 11-25 (Box 10)
- Chilton Lecture, University of Texas,School of Allied Health Sciences, Dallas, Texas, 1980 January 28-30 (Box 10)
- Rockefeller University Council Meeting, 1980 January 16 (Box 10)
- Extinct Commitments, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
- Lecture in Cell Biology Course (Cells and Organelles), New York University School of Medicine, 1982 December 13 (Box 10)
- ASCB (American Society for Cell Biology) Meeting, 1982 November 30-December 4 (Box 10)
- Gordon Conference on Lysosomes, 1982 June 28-July 2 (Box 10)
- New York Society of Electron Microscopy, Lecture, Caspary Hall, Rockefeller University (RU), 1981 December 9 (Box 10)
- Pfizer, Incorporated (Seminar), "Drug Targeting", Groton, Connecticut, 1981 December 3 (Box 10)
- New York Academy of Sciences, International Conference on Peroxisomes of Glyoxysomes, 1981 September 9-11 (Box 10)
- Eli Lilly and Company, "Cellular Aspects of Inflammation", Boston, 1981 June 2 (Box 10)
- Boston Meetings (Eli Lilly), 1981 June 2 (Box 10)
- 9th Solomon A. Berson Memorial Lecture, Mt. Sinai School of Medicine, 1981 April 8 (Box 10)
- Theobald Smith Award, Albany, 1981 April 2 (Box 10)
- Thesis Evaluation, William Muller, Open Lecture (Rockefeller University (RU)), 1981 February 9 (Box 10)
- Seminar, Smith, Kline and French Laboratories, Philadelphia, 1981 January 28 (Box 10)
- Extinct Commitments, 1983 (Box 10)
- "Lysosomes in Medicine", Lecture in the Course "Molecular and Cellular Biology" for 1st Year Medical Students, New York University Medical Center, 1983 December 13 (Box 10)
- Conference on "The Molecular Basis of Lysosomal Storage Disorders", National Institute of Health (NIH), National Institute of Neurological and Communicative Disorders and Stroke, 1983 September 12-14 (Box 10)
- Thesis Defense, Bradley Arrick, Caspary-Rm. 1A (Rockefeller University (RU)), 1983 April 12 (Box 10)
- James Law Lecture, Cornell University, College of Veterinary Medicine, Ithaca, New York, 1983 April 7 (Box 10)
- Luncheon, The Salk Institute (Jonas Salk), San Diego, CA, 1983 February 7 (Box 10)
- Gordon Research Conference, "Role of Oxygen Radicals in Biology and Medicine":, Santa Barbara, California, 1983 February 7-13 (Box 10)
- Extinct Commitments, 1984 (Box 10)
- Lecture in "Molecular and Cellular Biology", Course, New York University (NYU) Medical Center, 1984 December 14 (Box 10)
- First-year PhD and MD-PhD "Orientation Lunch", Rockefeller University (RU) Tower, 1984 November 20 (Box 10)
- Mackenzie Lecture, The Mary Imogene Bassett Hospital, Cooperstown, New York, 1984 November 16 (Box 10)
- Third International Congress on Cell Biology, Tokyo, Japan, 1984 August 26-31 (Box 10)
- International Symposium on Proteinases and Intracellular Protein Catabolism, Lecture in Honor of Brian Poole, Airlie, Virginia, 1984 My 30-June 2 (Box 10)
- Rockefeller University Council Meeting, 1984 May 25 (Box 10)
- International Symposium "Membrane Biogenesis and Recycling", Biological and Medical Aspects, Japan, 1984 September 1-3 (Box 10)
- Extinct Commitments, 1985 (Box 11)
- Cell Biology Course, Lecture in "Molecular and Cellular Biology", New York University (NYU), 1985 December 18 (Box 11)
- Lecture in "Innovators in Biochemistry" Series, Medical College of Virginia,Richmond, Virginia, 1985 November 25 (Box 11)
- Thesis Presentation and Defense of Peter Hotez, 1985 November 12 (Box 11)
- Future of Experimental Biology, Montréal, 1985 September 22 (Box 11)
- 5th International Conference on Experimental Ulcer, Boston, 1985 May 16-18 (Box 11)
- Thesis Defense by David Lapay, Smith Annex, A33 (Rockefeller University (RU)), 1985 March 20 (Box 11)
- Talk, "Evening at Rockefeller University", Rockefeller University (RU), 1985 January 23 (Box 11)
- Lecture in "Innovators in Biochemistry" Series, Medical College of Virginia, Richmond, Virginia, 1985 November 25 (Box 11)
- Thesis Presentation and Defense of Peter Hotez, 1985 November 12 (Box 11)
- Future of Experimental Biology, Montréal, 1985 September 22 (Box 11)
- 5th International Conference on Experimental Ulcer, Boston, 1985 May 16-18 (Box 11)
- Thesis Defense by David Lapay, 1985 March 20 (Box 11)
- Talk-"Evening at Rockefeller University", Rockefeller University (RU), 1985 January 23 (Box 11)
- Extinct Commitments, 1986 (Box 11)
- Fritz Lipmann Memorial, 1986 December 12 (Box 11)
- 90th American Nobel Anniversary Dinner, New York, New York, 1986 December 9 (Box 11)
- National Library of Medicine Medal Award Ceremony, Washington, D. C., 1985 November 18 (Box 11)
- Pontifical Academy, Rome, 1986 October 27-30 (Box 11)
- Ad hoc Committee on Cell Biology, Appointment, Rockefeller University (RU), 1986 March 10 (Box 11)
- Annual Meeting, National Academy of Sciences, Washington, D. C., 1986 April 27-29 (Box 11)
- Talk to Donors, "A Guided Tour of the Living Cell", Rockefeller University (RU), 1986 March 4 (Box 11)
- Lecture, "Molecular and Cellular Biology", New York University (NYU) Medical Center, 1986 December 17 (Box 11)
- National Academy of Sciences, Regional Roundtable, Rockefeller University (RU), 1986 December 15 (Box 11)
- ASCB Meeting, Washington, D. C., 1986 December 7-11 (Box 11)
- Extinct Commitments, 1987 (Box 11)
- Scientific Birthday Party (for Christian de Duve), 1987 November 17 (Box 11)
- "Prebiotic Synthese and the Mechanism of Early Chemical Evolution", 1988 (Box 11)
- Fritz Lipmann Symposium, Berlin, 1987 October 5-6 (Box 11)
- Seminar on Prokaryote-Eukaryote Transition, 1987 April 23 (Box 11)
- Memorial Talk for Alex Novikoff, Albert Einstein College of Medicine, 1987 January 27 (Box 11)
- Extinct Commitments, 1988 (Box 11)
- FEBS Meeting, Prague, 1988 (Box 11)
- Biochemical Society, Danielli Lecture, London, 198 December 19 (Box 11)
- Ludwig Institute, Hotel Hilton (New York), 1988 December 11-13 (Box 11)
- Wolf Foundation, Rockefeller University, 1988 December 5-6 (Box 11)
- Julius Schultz Visiting Professor Lecture, University of Florida Medical School, Miami, Florida, 1988 November 28-30 (Box 11)
- 60th Birthday Dinner and Symposium for Norton Zinder, 1988 November 13 (Box 11)
- Workshop on "Biogenesis of Peroxisomes (Glyoxysomes, Glycosomes), Amsterdam, 1988 September 26-29 (Box 11)
- Proctor and Gamble, Consultation, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1988 April 13 (Box 11)
- Extinct Commitments, 1989 (Box 11)
- American Society for Cell Biology, Talk, "Of Lysosomes and Peroxisomes", Houston, Texas, 1989 November 9 (Box 11)
- Weizmann National Event, New York, 1989 October 29 (Box 11)
- Talk, Institut de Recherches Cliniques de Montréal, Montréal, 1989 June 2-4 (Box 11)
- Richard Wozniak, Thesis Talk/Defense, 1989 March 20, April 5 (Box 11)
- Luncheon of Scientific Attaches, Belgian Embassy, Washington, D. C., 1989 March 16 (Box 11)
- Extinct Commitments, 1990 (Box 11)
- American Society for Cell Biology, Annual Meeting, San Diego, California, 1990 December 9-13 (Box 11)
- Lecture, "The Origin of Life", Iona College, New Rochelle, New York, 1990 November 20 (Box 11)
- Sigma Xi, "Outstanding Scientist" Talk, Newark Chapter, University Medical and Dental School of New Jersey, 1990 May 17 (Box 11)
- New York Hall of Science, Biology Advisory Committee Meeting. Corona, Queens, New York, 1990 March 16 (Box 11)
- Extinct Commitments, 1991-1994 (Box 12)
- Lecture, University of South Carolina Medical School, Columbia, South Carolina, 1994 December 6-7 (Box 12)
- 7th ISSOL (International Society for the Study of the Origin of Life) Meeting and 10th International Conference on the Origin of Life, Plenary Lecture, "From Protometabolism to Metabolism", Barcelona, Spain, 1993 July 4-9 (Box 12)
- FEBS Advanced Course on Peroxisomes, Dijon, 1993 April (Box 12)
- Reception for NSTA (National Science Teachers Association) Honoring Nobelists, New York (NY) Academy of Sciences, 1992 November 20 (Box 12)
- American Philosophical Society, Autumn General Meeting, Philadelphia, 1992 November 12-13 (Box 12)
- 9th COSPAR Plenary Meeting, "The Origin of Biological Catalysis", Washington, D. C., 1992 September 3 (Box 12)
- Gordon Conference, Colby College, New London, New Hampshire, 1992 June 21-26 (Box 12)
- Honoris Causa, University of Montréal, 1992 May 29 (Box 12)
- American Philosophical Society (Trip Cancelled), Washington, D. C., 1992 April 26-29 (Box 12)
- National Academy of Sciences (Trip Cancelled), Washington, D. C., 1992 May 26-29 (Box 12)
- Nobel Jubilee, 90th Anniversary, Stockholm, 1991 December 4-11 (Box 12)
- Mt. Sinai Medical School, Lecture, 1991 November 13 (Box 12)
- American Philosophical Society, Autumn General Meeting, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1991 November 7-8 (Box 12)
- 150th Anniversary, Belgian Royal Academy of Medicine, Brussels, 1991 September 26-28 (Box 12)
- Enzyme Club, Lecture, 1991 April 17 (Box 12)
- Research Advisory Board Meeting, RCM, Montréal, 1991 April (Box 12)
- Neil Patterson Publishers Meeting, Houston, 1991 March 28-30 (Box 12)
- New York Academy of Sciences Lecture, "The Origin of Life", 1991 February 1991 (Box 12)
- Extinct Commitments, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
- Lecture, UMD New Jersey, Cancer Institute of New Jersey, New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1996 November 20 (Box 12)
- 7th Annual Chicago Humanities Festival, Chicago, Illinois, 1996 November 8-10 (Box 12)
- Lecture, "The Origin of Life", University of Scranton, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1995 November 13 (Box 12)
- Polanyi Chemistry Celebration, Toronto University, 1995 November 2-5 (Box 12)
- International Symposium on Peroxisomes, Biology and [its] Role in Toxicology and Disease, Aspen Institute, Aspen, Colorado, 1995 June 28-July 2 (Box 12)
- The Rockefeller University Council, Spring Meeting, 1995 April 6 (Box 12)
- Planning Meeting, Rockefeller University (RU) Council, RU President's Office, 1995 March 23 (Box 12)
- Talk at Spring Meeting of the Rockefeller University (RU) Council, 1995 April 6 (Box 12)
- Rockefeller University, "Journey into the Cell: Celebrating 50 Years of Electron Microscopy and Modern Cell Biology", 1995 March 16-17, Lecture, The Belgian Connection Roundtable (Box 12)
- Extinct Commitments, 1997 (Box 12)
- American Philosophical Society Talk, Autumn Meeting, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1997 November 14 (Box 12)
- Lecture, Sigma Xi, Oakland University, Rochester, Minnesota, 1997 April 17 (Box 12)
- Extinct Commitments, 1998 (Box 12)
- APS (American Philosophical Society), 1998 (Box 12)
- Pontifical Academy of Sciences, Plenary Session, Rome, 1998 October 26-29 (Box 12)
- California Trip, 1998 January (Box 12)
- Human Performance Laboratory, University of Calgary, 1998 January (Box 12)
- Extinct Commitments, 1998 (Box 12)
- John Templeton Foundation, Lyford Cay, Nassau (the Bahamas), 1998 November (Box 12)
- Workshop on Size Limits of Very Small Microorganisms (Box 12)
- Workshop on Size Limits of Very Small Microorganisms, 1998 October 22-23 (Box 12)
- Extinct Commitments, 1998-2000 (Box 12)
- Nature of Nature Conference, Baylor University, Waco, Texs, 2000 April 12-16 (Box 12)
- George Palade Symposium, La Jolla, California, 1999 March 24-26 (Box 12)
- Greenwich Academy, Talk to Students, Greenwich, Connecticut, 1998 December (Box 12)
- Foundation for the Future (Box 12)
- Many Worlds, The New Universe and Its Theological Implications, Lyford Cay, Nassau (the Bahamas), 1998 November 22-24 (Box 12)
- IOC Olympic Academy for Sports Sciences, New York, 2000 July 26 (Box 13)
- Laboratory and University Lectures (Box 13)
- Lab Seminars (ICP), 1990 May 18 (Box 13)
- Origin of Life Seminars (Box 13)
- Time/Life Books, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
- Time/Life Books, "The Cell", 1979 (Box 13)
- Muller, Miklos, Time/Life (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980 (Box 13)
- A-I (Box 13)
- J-R (Box 13)
- S-Z (Box 13)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Proposal Evaluations, etc. (Box 13)
- Rockefeller University Interoffice Correspondence (Box 13)
- Commitments, Tentative (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Refusals (Commitments) (Box 13)
- Derrick, Walter C., (Applicant Parasitology) (Box 13)
- Autograph Requests (Box 13)
- ICP General Correspondence (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-I, 1981 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-R, 1981 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1981 (Box 13)
- Autograph Requests, etc. (Box 13)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts and Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Commitment Refusals (Box 13)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Interoffice Correspondence (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-J, 1982 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, K-R, 1982 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1982 (Box 13)
- Autograph Requests, etc. (Box 13)
- Job Applications (Box 13)
- Possible Commitments (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Commitment Refusals (Box 13)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Interoffice Correspondence (Box 13)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts and Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-I, 1983 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-R, 1983 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1983 (Box 13)
- Job Applications (Box 13)
- Autograph Requests (Box 13)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 13)
- Interoffice Correspondence, University Bulletins (Box 13)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts or Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-H, 1984 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-P, 1984 (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1984 (Box 13)
- Autograph Requests (Box 13)
- Commitment Refusal (Box 13)
- Job Applications (Box 13)
- Interoffice Correspondence, University Bulletins (Box 13)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts or Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 13)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-H, 1985 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-R, 1985 (Box 14)